Dhanesh Kumar

Computer science student possessing the analytical abilities necessary for designing and developing mobile and web applications. Gained exposure to key concepts in react, MySQL, and data structures. Hand on experience of programming languages include JavaScript, Dart, C, C++, and python.

EXPERIENCE

Accenture, Remote — Developer Program

Feb 2022 - Feb 2022

Contribution in debugging algorithm, design changing to an existing architecture, and applied Unit testing on smallest testable parts of an application

Comfy Living, Remote — Amazon, and eBay store Manager

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

A USA based furniture company having store on both amazon and eBay. Virtual responsibilities order management processing and updating store

Fiverr, Remote — Freelancing

Jun 2019 - Present

worked on more than 20 projects in databases, data analysis and data preprocessing – Java, MySQL, regression, python.

EDUCATION

NUST, Islamabad — Bachelor

Sep 2018 - Present

Sindh Public College, Umerkot — *Pre* - Engineering

Feb 2016 - Mar 2018

PROJECTS

iTour (FYP) — Flutter, Firebase, PyTorch

- A cross platform mobile app platform to plan a fully customized trip of an area based on your interests and preferences.
- The platform enables users to plan visiting sights and book nearby hotels.

Shopit — JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and MySQL

- Designed and implemented the idea of distributed E-commerce marketplace
- Localize the e-commerce sales within a locality to enable quick delivery times and high availability at ease.

Manaj — Java, and MySQL

 Manages employee's salaries, deductions, other conveyance, net pay, bonuses, and generation of pay-slips

- Islamabad, Pakistan
- **9** 03473377700
- dmeghwar.bscs18seecs@seecs.edu.pk
- in www.linkedin.com/in/dhaneshkumar20/

SKILLS

React, JavaScript

C, C++, java, python

Data structures and algorithm

Position Responsibilities

Member Team Admin Events at 15th HONET- ICT international conference.

External relation at NUST community service club

Deputy Director Marketing at SGA (Student Government Association)

Achievements

Excellence performance award by united helping hand foundation (UNIHHFO).

Certification of Completion in software engineering by Forage

Professional Interest

Mobile Application
Web Application
Competitive programming

Hobbies

Esports Cricket

TV shows